At this point we're talking about securing the artwork to the thermographic paper.
I personally glove up when I do this because of the purple ink seems just to get everywhere.
So at this point, I got gloves on, I've got the thermograph paper cut to size.
I've got the customer's artwork that I have positioned vertically as opposed to horizontally.
Which he picked the font out online.
So I'm going to secure it to the paper here by doing this.
Using some surgical tape and you don't want the image to shift around because you don't want any ghosting of the images.
As you can see, some of this line work here is very detailed and very defined.
And you know it's a very simple piece, but there's no room for error with this.
So what we do is we secure the artwork to here using surgical tape.
And we have two choices that we can use.
We can use one, a ball point pen or we can use a mechanical pencil.
The ball point pen is usually better because you can press harder and it gets a better transfer on the hand drawing of these stencils.
But now the mechanical pencil is a finer type.
And in this particular case, that is what we need.
So I'm going to use the mechanical pencil on this particular one.
I'm going to press hard and I'm going to get the nice crisp detail.
And I'm going to show you how to do that.